Did Kaori-senpai just barely make it?
Right? I mean, she won but still...
She seemed to be struggling.
Kaori...
I wonder if something happened.
Welcome home, Ami!
Here, I bought rubbers.
Did you already creampie her?
Well, I'm almost there.
Hurry... The rubber... Hurry!
No, don't do that!
Ah, that's right. Kaori-senpai...
Masaya-senpai sent a message.
All four of us are gonna have an overnight
study group this coming weekend.
Huuuh, her boyfriend will join us!?
We have no choice. He's suspecting me.
Saying no to him would only spell trouble.
It's gonna be fine, Ryou-kun!
If you do as I say,
we'll end up having a fun time instead!
Mayhem
It's Saturday. Masaya-kun actually came to this house.
This study group is one big lie.
But there's no way I could tell him that.
Since that day I got violated here in Sasaki-san's house,
I've been having sex here with them almost every day.
I couldn't go against them since
they've pictured and filmed me a lot.
I've stopped speaking out against it lately.
I've started to think less and less
about the fact that they are raping me.
Having sex here after school has become
a normal thing for me now.
Kaori-senpai...
Huh, what is it? This question?
Whoa...
This is bad... Out of all times,
I had to pop a boner right now...
Let's take our baths, then.
You can go first, Kaori-senpai.
O-Okay, thanks...
Alright, I'll go take a dump.
No way! That's so nasty, Ryou-kun!
Whoa!?
Lemme fuck you, Kaori-senpai!
Hold on, what are you doing!?
Well, you see... I've been studying
the whole day. I'm at my limit already.
Weren't you waiting for this as well?
Let's relieve each other!
No, Masaya-kun is right in the other room!
There you go again, acting like you hate this.
We can't!
If you do that, I'm...
Let's get to it right away!
A mere apology won't cut it!
We're doing such a thing when Masaya-kun is nearby!
Please pull it out already.
Masaya-kun is nearby.
I don't wanna come! Please...
I'm begging you, please pull it out!
Does having your boyfriend nearby make a difference?
Just be a pervert who gets off that instead, Senpai!
Hey, what are you... W-Wait...
Ehhhh!?
Masaya-senpai...
You got hard while looking at our panties earlier, right?
Don't do this, Sasaki-san...
Ah, no need to call me by my name.
You can just think of me as
nothing more than a cock sleeve.
Ahh, no way...
K-Kaori...
Come on! What now, Kaori-senpai?
Your pussy is twitching like crazy now!
Doesn't that mean you're reaching climax?
N-No, I don't wanna come!
I'd normally shove a finger up your ass right now
and enjoy watching your o-face.
That's too bad, though.
I'll have to leave you turned on and hanging.
That's what Ami told me.
You came thrice, Masaya-senpai.
U-Umm, Masaya-kun... Are you still up?
Eh? Yeah...
Can we hold hands?
I calmed down... I knew it.
This relaxes me the most.
But this won't do...
Since we stopped halfway earlier,
my body won't cool down!
I'm sorry, Masaya-kun...
Wanna go all the way with me right now?
Whoa, they're going at it!
What's the point of letting them fuck?
Even if we turn Kaori-senpai into a slut,
her boyfriend's bare innocence
would probably fix her back.
However...
If they are to have sex right now...
She would definitely end up comparing the two of you.
But just to be sure,
I also went on and sucked her boyfriend's semen out!
I see...
So that's why she has that odd look
on her face since earlier.
You drained him and couldn't get it stiff enough.
But there's even more to it, Kaori-senpai!
When you have sex with that dimwit,
Whether you're with us or your boyfriend,
you would be sex-craved all the time!
Just one more push...
...and you would be beneath me!
Guidance Office
I'll be on my way...
How did it go, Kaori?
If I don't show good results
in this weekend's practice game,
I will be removed from our team's regular lineup.
I had it coming. Forget about the tournament,
I even lose against my juniors at rallies.
Even I am aware that I'm a failure of an ace player.
It'll be alright. I'll work hard enough
for two people in our doubles match.
Use that time to break out of your slump.
Yes... Thank you...
Hello!
Kaori-senpai, I saw you coming out
of the guidance office earlier.
Are you finally quitting the team?
There's no way I would!
Is that so? My parents are gonna be away this weekend.
It would be a chance to have as much sex as you want.
I bet you'd only be having some
lousy practice game, anyway.
That's too bad. Work hard out there and win.
Whatever the case may be,
you're still the club president!
Kaori... Kaori...
Masaya-kun...
Kaori, I'm gonna come...
Kaori, how was it today?
Right... It felt very good...
I do manage to reach mild orgasms.
Just a bit whenever we kiss.
But at that point, Masaya-kun would usually be done.
That's why I couldn't reach that mind-numbing climax.
Masaya-kun can't give it to me.
I wanna come harder!
Kitamura! Is she not here?
Kaori, if you can't win today...
You'll lose your place here.
Feels good... It feels good!
Y-Yes, this is it! I love this!
What do you think? I called it, right?
Yeah, Senpai actually skipped her match!
Well, more like she was at a loss up to the last minute
and ended up choosing to go here instead.
Since Kaori-senpai ditched tennis to come here,
I will reward her with yet another kind of pleasure...
...as a gift!
This is on another level...
This feels good on another level!
Should I even learn about this?
After all, this is something Masaya-kun can't give me!
I'm almost there!
I can feel a huge one coming since earlier!
I'm gonna keep ramming you, then!
Shove it in! Keep thrusting!
Here it is! It's a huge orgasm!
Coming! I'm coming!
Huh!?
Masaya-senpai is now nothing more than
a boyfriend who sucks at sex for her.
She lost her place in the tennis club as well.
Next would be swapping our social standing.
What do you think, Ryou-kun? Does this suit me?
Ohh, nice! You look great!
You're okay with me taking this. Am I right, Kaori?
Yes, I don't need that uniform anymore...
I'm quitting the club...
From now on, I want to be
pleasured a lot every single day...
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji